(Howard:)Do you think
(Dr Gallo:)he's perpetuating
that relationship
(Dr Gallo:)by seeking out
a partner like you?
(Sheldon:)You know,
I used to wear tank tops a lot.
(Penny:)That was a big selling point.
(Amy(on Skype):)Hi, Sheldon. What's up?
(Sheldon:)Good news. You're an asteroid.
(Amy:)Uh... please tell me
what to say next.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps I should explain.
(Sheldon:)While working with Koothrappali,
(Sheldon:)we discovered an asteroid,
and I named it after you.
(laughs):
Oh.
(Amy:)Sheldon, thank you.
(Amy:)That's so romantic.
(Amy:)But what about Rajesh?
(Amy:)He was okay with
you choosing the name?
(Sheldon:)Well, it took
a little negotiating,
(Sheldon:)but I wore him down.
(Sheldon:)Uh, we get the asteroid,
(Sheldon:)and if you and I have children,
(Sheldon:)they all have to be
named Rajesh.
(Amy:)All of them?
(Sheldon:)Even the girls.